 const STORE = [
    {
     question: 'Which franchise is the character Mario from?',
     answer: [
          'Nintendo','Sony', 'Microsoft', 'Ubisoft'
     ],
     correct: 'Nintendo'
    },
    {
     question: "What genre of game is Super Mario World(SNES)?",
     answer: [
         'First Person Shooter','Role Playing Game', 'Platformer', 'Action/Adventure'
     ],
     correct:'Platformer'
    },
    {
     question: 'What does MMORPG stand for?',
     answer:[
         'Mega Morphesis Open Role-Playing Game' ,
         'Mighty Multiplayer Open Role Person Game',
         'Massively Multiplayer Online Role-Playing Game',
         'Mini Mega Only Real PLaying Game',
     ],
     correct:'Massively Multiplayer Online Role-Playing Game'
    },
    {
    question: "What game is classified as a first person shooter (FPS)?",
    answer: [
        'God of War','Resident Evil Series','Call of Duty','Fortnite'
    ],
    correct:'Call of Duty'
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the Final Fantasy series is the character Cloud Strife from?",
    answer:[
        'Final Fantasy 8','Final Fantasy 11','Final Fantasy 7','Final Fantasy 3'
    ],
    correct:'Final Fantasy 7'
    },
    {
    question: "Which game is considered a Multiplayer Online Battle Arena (MOBA)?",
    answer:[
        'Red Dead Redemption 2','Fire Emblem','Overwatch','League of Legends'
    ],
    correct:'League of Legends'
    },
    {
    question: "Which video game is a Battle Royale?",
    answer: [
        'Starcraft','PUBG','Diablo 3','Until Dawn'
    ],
    correct:'PUBG'
    },
    {
    question: "What is the genre of game that features turn based combat?",
    answer: [
        'Role Playing Game','3rd Person Shooter','Open World Adventure','Sports'
    ],
    correct:'Role Playing Game',
    },
    {
    question: "Which of these is a Roguelike video game?",
    answer: [
        'Hollow Knight','Metal Gear Solid','God of War','Binding of Isaac'
    ],
    correct:'Binding of Isaac'
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the following characters is from Street Fighter?",
    answer: [
        'Heihachi','Pikachu','Cami','Ahri'
    ],
    correct:'Cami'
    }
];
 

